Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living creature was hurt
during the production of this film.
Osman is here!
What would you like us to do, sir?
Soldiers will be in defensive formation.
What can Osman do to us Commander Mouzalon?
You don't know Osman, Commander.
I'm sure the troops in the west
thought the same!
I do not want arrogance!
I want victory!
Will Osman really attack?
Osman is not crazy.
He would not attack such an army
before preparing.
But I am also not stupid.
I will take all my precautions.
I'll be ready when he comes.
Come at me, Lord.
Come...
Even our presence here frightens you.
My Bey, when should we attack them?
What is your order?
My Bey...
Valiants from all tribes....
...came here to kill the Lord.
Today, this will be done if Allah permits!
They are crowded but we will attack from all sides
when our Bey orders us.
We've been waiting for this day
for a long time, my Bey
In the name of Allah, my Bey!
My Bey!
Now the field is ours, huh?
Right.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
What are Orhan and Alaeddin doing?
Did they go to Bapheus?
They must be settled on the left and right,
at a distance of one ell.
My Bey, the Alps who came from tribes for the fight
settled on the left and right in...
...Bafeus with your order.
My Bey, most of our Alps are there.
What about us?
We will attack as
a wolf attacks a herd, if Allah permits.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
My Bey... Our number is not enough.
We'll be defeated.
That's what we want.
Come on, archers!
Apparently that coward will not come here.
Commander Mouzalon.
If you allow us,
the army will break the formation.
I told you that you don't know Osman,
Commander.
Anything can happen anytime.
The army came here to fight.
-They will fight.
-Osman does not have the courage to att...
You idiot!
Wall of shield!
O Truth!
(One of the names of Allah: Haqq)
Shoot them!
O Truth!
Come at me, Osman.
Come..
What is your order, Commander Mouzalon?
They are attacking from all sides.
But they are weak.
This army can not be defeated,
Commander Silvanus.
A little bit more patience.
The only thing that making them
resist right now..
...is their faith.
They will lose it soon.
Allah is the greatest!
Shield wall!
Attack!
Come on!
Come to me!
What will you do now, Osman?
The shepherd's fate...
...is to be defeated by Byzantine.
Wolves will tear apart the heartless lions.
Be patient, Lord.
Be patient!
Alps.
Retreat!
Falling back!
I will show you.
Bring the horses.
Now they think we are defeated.
But in the end, victory will be ours.
It is our turn now.
We will fall back to Bapheus.
Orhan Bey and Alaeddin Bey..
...must be settled now, right Bey?
True.
Let us retreat to our point...
...then we will weaken them with arrows.
Then, victory is ours.
Those who try to capture Turks' homeland
will lose their head quick.
Of course. That's right.
Konur, you will continue to retreat with valiants.
-They'll think we are perished, they'll follow us.
-As you command, Bey.
Aktemur, you will head left.
As you command, Bey.
Bala and others,
you will come after us.
We will not look back until Bapheus.
Let us go.
Stop!
This could be a trap of Osman's.
The tracks divide here, Commander Mouzalon.
Doesn't matter, we will not.
If Osman is up to some ambush..
The army must be big enough to handle it.
Sir, he was hurt.
He left without looking back.
You still think that?
I will not underestimate Osman again.
They army will go this way..
In one piece.
O Truth!
Allah is the greatest!
Lord.
You cannot escape your end, Osman.
That means you cannot escape me!
No.
My army is the strongest army of Byzantium.
None of your games...
...will be enough to defeat it.
Break those hands that shot us arrows!
Tear those eyes that targeted Byzantium!
My soldiers!
The victory shall be ours today!
The arrows will always be on your chests.
Our eyes will always
be looking towards your lands!
The victory will always belong to Turks!
Alps, attack!
Why are you so furious, Esrigun Hatun?
I thought the only traitor was Nayman.
But it seems the world is full of traitors, Bala Hatun.
We told you, the order is
different here in these lands.
Come on!
Esrigun!
When the wolves arrive at the field,
the jackals run away!
The lion does not fit in the cage,
it tears it up, pierce them, pierce them!
No one can threaten Kayi,
Allah is the greatest! Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest!
Valens.
You will understand.
You will understand that
Byzantium will destroy you.
We understand power, come on and teach me.
You will understand that
we will always beat Byzantium!
You're dreaming, Osman.
Byzantium does not lose.
When this battle is over and you lose your head,
you will understand that Byzantium
can lose just like everyone else.
-We're going back to Bursa.
-We can still win.
I know which battle can be won
and which will be lost.
We're going back.
I will come back Osman!
You will hit once, and I will come back
to hit a thousand times.
Osman!
Run anywhere you want,
you will not be able to run away from me.
He cannot run anywhere father!
Come on!
No, Orhan!
Baysungur, Turahan go after Orhan!
You cannot enter the Turkish lands
so easily, Commander.
This is our land, silly!
For now, come here.
Come here.
Come here, come.
So,
the lands you came to shed our blood
will be your grave.
Then we will get into the
same ground together, Osman.
But there will be a difference.
You become carcass when you
we become martyr when we die.
Alps.
Take all the treasury
in the ships they came from.
Now, we will go to Koyunhisar right away.
-Yes my Bey!
-Come on.
-Come on Alps!
Allah is eternal!
Allah is right!
We need to get over the walls
before Osman Bey arrives, come on!
The infidel army is here!
We have to take this citadel, come on!
Allah is eternal!
Allah is right!
Soldiers! Attack!
Leo. We are going back to Bursa!
Boran Bey! Turahan!
Your life is yours today.
When the right time comes
I'll take both your life and Bursa.
Allah is eternal!
Allah is right!
Allah is eternal! Allah is right!
We can't break it!
Brother, either we conquer this castle...
...or we will become martyrs here!
Come on!
We will not let Osman Bey down, my brother!
Allah is the greatest!
Osman died when fighting against our armies!
Our army will be here soon!
You will all die!
Do not bow down, Alps! Don't!
Hit stronger! Stronger!
Come on! We will not return!
The army is coming, my Bey! Let's go back!
We will not return!
This is the hill of archers today!
Harder!
Allah is eternal!
Allah is right!
Allah is eternal! Allah is right!
Ignore the infidels!
Allah is eternal!
Allah is right!
We arrived, Alps!
Thank you Beys!
Live long!
Come on Alps!
Allah is eternal!
Allah is right!
O Allah!
Allah is eternal!
Allah is right!
Muslims started fighting!
Infidels will get lost!
The flag of Islam will be planted everywhere!
Come on brothers!
Allah is the greatest!
-Come on Alps!
-If their doors are made of steel...
...we have hearts made of steel!
Praise be!
-O Allah! O Allah!
-We are here, Lord! We will take this castle!
Come on! Come on Beys!
O Allah!
That dog.
Mouzalon.
In the name of Allah,
the most merciful, the most compassionate.
I will take both your life and Bursa!
I will.
He was waiting for us to come after, Orhan Bey.
He was indeed, and he will wait more.
I will take that castle..
And that borrowed throne of his.
-If Allah permits.
Innkeeper, bring us bulghur with meat.
We will stay here tonight.
We will arrive Yenisehir first thing in the morning.
Mouzalon expects ineptness from me.
Expects me to act without planning.
However, he is wrong.
-Let me renew my ablution.
-Okay my Bey.
Orhan Bey.
You are Orhan Bey, right?
I am Irem
I am the aide of Lady Holofira.
She always speak of you.
Holofira.
Where is she now? Is she okay?
Tell me, Hatun?
We'll leave soon, come here.
Holofira.
She remembers me.
Aktemur Bey.
What is this infidel doing here?
Bey knows what he's doing, Bayindir Bey.
You will find out soon.
Make way, Osman Bey.
Welcome.
Now, Bey's wonder..
What are these Christians doing here?
And you..
Wonder why you are here.
Since we will live together..
Then we will talk the principles together.
Koyunhisar Castle is ours now.
Now tell me.
What do you think about this.
Of course, speech does lead to beheadings.
However, don't worry.
We will welcome your words.
We are grieved, Osman Bey. We are scared.
We are scared about Koyunhisar's situation.
Tell me.
Why are you scared?
You are scared of torment.
Of injustice.
However, know this.
Under my banner, none of these exist.
This council is established with merit.
Even..
The first principle is ethics.
We observed you in castles forts.
Even..
We saved Leodis, whom you scorned
because he was a shepherd.
We told him to give us one sheep.
We offered five times the price.
However..
He did not sell us.
As the sheep's time was not yet.
And that is why he is in this council.
We've watched you as well.
The most fair among you
will represent your people.
You will talk about their problems in this council.
However, never forget this.
If torment enters one home..
Then law is applied.
The law is the same for all of us.
Those who are not..
A traitor and a degenerate..
Is the same for the law.
Even if their nation, their religion
and their tongue is different..
They are the same for us.
That is why..
Your life, your riches and your family..
Is under my security.
Even if you say so..
Even if you think us the same as one of you..
As you say then, okay.
Thank you.
Now be with your people.
Hear them.
Hear their problems, and tell us in this council.
Don't forget this as well..
You will not be taxed for
any business you do with Byzantine.
And I will protect your caravans...
...to Byzantium.
I hope our business will grow.
Farewell now.
My Bey forgive me, but...
Thank Allah a thousand times...
..we ruined all those Lords.
We went and took
the lands you said and wanted.
But..
What is doing business without gold in Byzantium?
I could not understand it.
Is that so, Bayindir?
Is that so?
You will do that.
You will go to the Constantine.
Osman, who lived in a tent until yesterday...
...set his eyes on our lands.
He and the Turkmens who follow him...
...deserved this punishment.
We cannot send Turks away from our lands
right away when Osman dies, sir.
Osman...
Thank God...
...we will not hear that shepherd's
name here again.
Sir.
Osman damaged Konya...
...as much as he damaged us.
Konya gave the flag itself.
And Osman will die today.
Now Turkmens who settled
on our lands will lose all their hopes.
First, Inegol...
..Bilecik, Sogut and Konya.
We will take every piece of land that Osman steps on.
I swear on Jesus.
My Osman Bey, forgive me but...
...why would that great Emperor...
...hear the words of a poor man like me?
Go and see him there.
He might not be that great, huh?
Don't you always cloud the issue?
Didn't you save your head
with your tongue for many times?
Don't worry. This duty...
...suits you the best.
We can sacrifice our lives for the cause.
I see that our Osman Bey...
...is prepared to sacrifice this poor man's head...
...it is the order of our Bey. We'll do as he says.
There is a law of war.
They came to wash our lands with blood.
And they lost.
There will be a price, of course.
Whoever will trade with our people in Byzantium...
...will not give gold in any way.
And the Emperor Andronikos...
...will ensure their safety.
Bayindir...
You will make him accept this.
Yes my Bey.
But you will not go there as the messenger of a tribe...
...you will be the messenger of an independent Beylic.
Emperor Andronikos will understand that...
...we are an independent Beylic...
...that depends on no one.
-It is time brother.
-That's right.
It's time.
We have been fighting
since my ancestor Ertugrul Gazi.
We have always moved towards them,
they have always attacked us.
We hit their commanders and their lords.
We took their citadels we took their castles.
And then
they faced us with their best armies.
And we ruined them in Bapheus area.
And
we did it all alone.
And as of now
it's our time to declare
that we are an independent Beylik.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
Inform everyone.
Send messengers to all the Beyliks.
Let everyone know that
we are an independent Beylik.
Yes my Bey.
Come on. Let's go to our people
and tell them the good news.
Osman repelled the Byzantium
is that so, Dursun Fakih?
He did, mighty Sultan.
And he did it all alone.
We did as we promised
and we sent the army, Dursun Fakih.
We did, but
forgive me, my Sultan.
Wasn't that our responsibility?
Don't speak in circles
say that you're on the throne thanks to Osman
but you cannot even help him with an army.
Of course not.
I do not hold you responsible for what happened,
but
but Osman Bey is destroying the infidels all alone.
He is the hope of Turkmens.
Don't you think
it is time for him to declare that
he is an independent Bey with your warrant?
So you're trying to say that
Osman should break his connection with Konya.
This will only divide us.
Show respect.
Commander. Show respect.
We show respect to Tabriz.
Not to Konya.
The amount of tax
we will collect from your merchants...
..is written here.
Sultan Mesud will..
...impress his seal.
Merchants will not be able to object.
If you enter this door like this again...
...you will not even have the tongue...
...to ask permission from Tabriz.
Turk-Islam state under the shadow of Mongols.
Seljuk State.
Konya.
Ha, Dursun Faqih?
When our reputation, which our ancestors glorified...
...is down here, what are you talking
about Sultan? you ask, right?
I'd behead him here if it wouldn't harm...
...all the people.
But the situation is clear, my Sultan.
While our hands are tied..
...Osman Bey's victories increase
Turk's reputation and hope.
We cannot ignore this.
There's no point in trying more, huh?
Astagfurullah Sultan Hadhrat.
But if the candle is blew out somewhere...
...it gives its fire to somewhere else.
The khutbah you will recite for Osman Bey...
...will befit your dignity.
Being blind to the truth...
...is the biggest cruelty.
You are right, Dursun Faqih.
Send news to ulamas you trust the most.
They should get ready.
I want to see them tomorrow in my palace.
Yes, Hadhrat Sultan.
Great Pope, the leader of Christians...
...Byzantium is defeated.
The cross is defeated.
The Emperor is a coward.
Commanders are idiot.
Lords do not know how to fight.
Soldiers don't have faith.
The fear of asking help from Catholics...
...made us lose against Turks.
I am begging you, dear Pope.
The cross that fell must rise again.
Our lands in the east are suffering.
Barbarians are invading our noble homeland.
The cross is giving the sky to the crescent.
Preventing this...
...is the most important duty of every Christian.
Christians' protector, sacred Pope.
Send a big crusaders army to these lands.
As Commander Mouzalon I promise you.
I will kill all your enemies.
O, The Tenacious!
O, The Opener, my Allah..
My Allah..
We thank You, my Allah.
Thank You..
...You granted us with a glorious victory.
My Allah...
Now grant me with doing justice
to this glorious victory.
Let me rule with justice...
...let me fly the flag of Islam...
...everywhere in the world...
...to give the poor what they deserve.
My Allah..
The ways of Your cause never end.
There are still many of them.
But..
..but our case...
..is The Red Apple.
(Turkish legend symboling the ultimate goal of conquest)
My Allah... To reach there...
...give us strength, my Allah...
Amen... Amen, my Allah..
Amen..
Boran Alp!
Are you running away from me?
No, why would I run away from you?
My Bey might order me something
I should check on him.
No.
You're running away.
You're running away from me since you
protected me during the battle.
About that.
Right, about that.
Didn't I tell you that do not risk your life for me?
-Why would you still...
-How can a human stop this, Esrigun Hatun?
I understood that
if you are hurt,
it hurts me more.
Boran brother, come on brother. Brother.
Come on brother.
O' ulema who taught the spirit and
mind of the people of Seljuks.
Now it is your turn for the conquest.
But this will not be like others.
This journey will be like
Eyup Ensari's journey to Constantinople.
From now on
you will spend your life behind Osman Bey.
We saw it with our own eyes.
The light went out here.
For those who always seek expeditions, the paths
are always like the gates of Heaven, my Sultan.
We planted many seeds in Konya
now it is time to plant them in Sogut, in Yenisehir
and even Bursa, and time to revive them.
This is your duty and your goal, Dursun Fakih.
As Osman Bey carries the banner all over the world.
you will prosper the Beylik
which he built.
If one side of Seljuks is science,
the other side is knowledge.
If its one post is ulema,
the other one is saints.
Now it is time to be the wings of
Osman Bey's Beylik.
Also
after tonight,
all the khutbah will be delivered
in the name of Osman Bey, not me.
This is Sultan Mesut's verdict.
Let them know, Dursun Fakih.
Yes, my Sultan.
We will let them know.
-Have a safe journey.
-Amen.
Orhan.
What happened son?
Son?
Even the best hunters might lose their prey.
Don't worry.
I know, but
I was sure that I was going to catch Valens, father.
If I had killed them, the martyrs
would have been resting in comfort now.
But I couldn't do it father.
I couldn't.
Son, look at me.
That dastard ran away for now.
But, about the martyrs.
When we declare our independence
all of them will rest in peace, don't worry.
Their end will eventually come.
It will, don't worry son.
But now it is time for us to tell our
independence to the people.
Let all of them know
that they belong to an independent Beylik.
My Bey!
We have news from Sultan Mesut, my Bey.
Praise be!
Praise be, Sultan Mesut.
Thank you.
What does he say, my Bey?
Oh, son.
He gave us the good news.
From now on
we have received the news we've been waiting for.
Commander Tatius.
Why are you in a hurry?
I've brought important news for Lord Valens.
What's this important news?
We got news from our spies in Konya.
A group of people that contains
wise men will set out to see Osman.
That group shall never arrive get the soldiers ready.
It shouldn't be so crowded just pick the best ones.
We will destroy them.
Won't we let the Lord know about it?
No.
We don't need the Lord and a huge army
to choke them in their own blood.
Come on.
We have a long way ahead but it is pretty beautiful.
We will teach a word
and every word we teach
will turn into a lot of sentences.
-The Frontiers will be the cradle of science.
-Amen.
The fire we set in Konya
will flare up in Osman Bey's Beylik,
if Allah permits!
Osman Bey's brave Alps'
Praise be!
So, at this rate wouldn't leave.
An infidel land, you would add them into ours.
Thank you, Kara Ebe, thank you.
-Groom.
-Mother.
Take Gurbuz and feed him alright?
Mother.
Gurbuz is full, and he doesn't like grass, he likes meat.
Cerkutay.
Are you mad? I am not talking about that Gurbuz.
I am talking about this Gurbuz.
You stubborn goat who ate my flowers.
Mother, I have just came back
from the battle, don't do this.
Alps, do you see this?
He calls me mother, and doesn't do what I say.
You have no heart.
With this old age and my aching legs..
With this pain in my waist.
Cerkutay, don't do this. She is tired as you can see.
What would happen
if you take Gurbuz to feed anyways?
Don't do this brother.
You have no heart, Cerkutay.
He will do it mother hand him the goat.
Here.
Now you regret giving that goat my name.
I got it.
Well done groom.
Look at me, take good care of it.
Do not let anything happen to it.
No, mother.
My Gurbuz, my goat.
Look, eat well okay?
Well done my valiant.
Alright then.
Why did I even get this.
She loves this goat more than me.
Gur buz brother, Bey is waiting for us.
We will head to Osman Bey.
And Cerkutay is off to feeding, let us go.
Where?
-Come on Cerkutay.
-Boran
Come on Cerkutay, to feeding.
-To feeding.
-Come on brother.
Gurbuz.
Where to? I will not leave Bey alone.
Boran don't go.
What will I do now?
Ah Cerkutay, ah!
Alps!
-To whom do these belong to?
-To Osman Bey, Cerkutay Alp.
Then..
Take this.
Here.
Come on.
Didn't they tell us to slaughter two goats?
That is what I know as well, brother.
-Let us go then.
-Come on.
So you are a messenger of Osman Bey.
After destroying my army, and conquering my forts..
Did you come here to beg for his life?
The Almighty Emperor.
As you said.
Why would The Mighty Osman Bey..
...who defeated your armies..
...who took what he wanted
whenever he wanted to..
...beg for mercy from you?
Osman thinks he won?
Not at all.
The Almighty Emperor.
Why would anyone "think" that?
It is a fact that Osman Bey has won.
If you're not going to beg for mercy,
then why are you here messenger?
For the agreement..
That Osman Bey will give to you.
What agreement?
From now on.
Even if muslim or not..
Any merchant from our people..
Will not pay a toll..
While doing business in your land.
They will do their business freely in your lands.
With that, you..
Will pay for two of tenth worth of your caravans..
When they enter our lands..
To Osman Bey as tax.
These are the words of Osman.
Look at that shepherd Osman.
Emperor Andronikos.
You do not have the messenger..
Of shepherd Osman in front of you.
And not even the messenger of..
Seljuk State's margrave Osman Bey.
Now, you have the messenger of..
Osman Bey, who does not answer to anyone..
Who is the only ruler of his lands, the ruler
of free people, Osman Bey.
You better speak knowing who you are speaking with.
Make way, Osman Bey.
Osman Bey is here.
Thank you.
Live long!
Thank you. Thank you.
We..
...did everything we said until now.
But we did all those things...
..thanks to you.
Our ancestors rode their horses to these lands.
Their intention was to turn these
ands into their homeland.
And we turned it into our homeland,
thank Allah.
First, we started with a tribe.
Then we gathered our tribes, we grew..
..but as we grew..
...the Byzantium always tried to attack us.
But..
...we defeated them at Bapheus alone.
On this cause we set out..
...with 200 tents, we took thousands of tents...
..tens of castles.
May Allah bless you.
Of course there was going to be a reward...
...for all the trouble, problems and torment.
Now we sent our messenger...
.. to Byzantium.
We will make an agreement with them.
From now on..
...you will not give any gold..
...when you are doing business with Byzantium.
Thus, the goods you sell will be cheaper...
..and your business will grow.
May Allah bless you!
Now, let's talk about the other issue.
From now on..
..khutbahs..
..will be recited in our name.
My Bey! What will Sultan Mesud say to this?
Khutbahs were recited for him!
No... Don't worry.
Sultan Mesud knows this..
...and he even consents to this.
Thus, now...
...he is sending the most talented scholars,
judges and teachers.
And thus...
...first, we will establish madrasas.
Then...
...we will place judges in every fortresses.
And scholars...
..scholars will..
...answer all of your questions.
Don't worry. There won't be a problem.
And business... Our business will grow...
...it will rise and if Allah permits...
-...it will be blessed.
-if Allah permits.
May Allah bless you Osman Bey!
Now it is time to share the trophy of Bapheus.
Come on Alps!
Share the trophy with our people.
O, people...
Now..
..we will become an independent Beylic!
Now... send the good news to everywhere!
To all Beylics! To all tribes!
Tell everyone!
I will be waiting for everyone to Sogut tonight.
Thank you.
Thank you too.
May Allah bless you too.
You will pay for this impudency, messenger.
Emperor Andronikos.
Even if you take my head now
it will not change the truth.
You were defeated! Right!
If you cannot agree I will die here.
But... all your people will die with me!
Why is that?
If you allow me. I'll tell you.
Let him.
Let him waste his last breath for this.
Be careful, Emperor.
Don't be scared.
Are you even scared of the Turks' map?
Look, Emperor.
These are the lands ruled by my Osman Bey.
And that means..
..your traders and caravans...
...have to step on our lands to do business.
Your wheat trade..
..is under our control.
I am talking about wheat, Emperor.
I am talking about bread and food.
Your warehouses are empty!
Without the caravans that will come from the east...
...all your people will die of hunger!
If you are going to say "I'll bring it with ships."...
..then..
...we will stop them with Karasi Bey.
Now, Emperor...
...if we agree here and if I go back...
...you will pay your tax,
take your goods and do your trade.
If you insist on taking my head...
..I assure you..
...I can sacrifice it for my lands.
If you cut my head off...
..I swear to Allah..
...not a single caravan...
...will arrive in the Constantine.
Not two of tenth.
-One of tenth.
-No.
Allah forbid.
There is no backing up in Osman Bey's matters.
Between you and me, he is very headstrong.
Otherwise..
Here is my head, Emperor.
This head..
In return of your own people.
Bring the clerk.
Elhamdulillah.
Bey.
Thank Allah.
We will send the heads of those who left from Konya.
Turks will see that our swords are so close to them.
Commander Tatius, I don't want any setbacks.
Our spies are watching every step of the caravan.
-They are going to your death. -Let them come.
We will show them the ending they deserve.
We will wash our swords with their blood.
Aktemur.
It is your duty to welcome
those who come from Konya.
As you command, Bey.
Thank you.
Konur...
This Lord dog is unpredictable.
It is your duty to protect the caravan.
As you command, Bey.
I will protect them at the cost of my life.
Thank you.
Come on Alps, on horses.
As you command, Bey. My sons..
And we will bring feathers to our ancestors.
Let us go.
They are approaching.
We will attack on my command.
Be ready.
What do you think you're doing?
-Get out of our way.
-We will.
After killing you all.
Those who put State of Seljuks against them
are bound to be destroyed.
This is my last warning.
Get out of our way.
You talk a lot. I will get your head first.
Then the people behind you.
They are many, we can not prevail.
We will delay them.
-Run to the forest.
-A Turk running is unheard of.
At the best, we fight to die.
Attack!
Why do they not like all these scholars, brothers?
Osman Bey has put the infidels to the ground.
Now, everyone is behind him.
Thank Allah.
Grand victories are loud.
They go over seas and mountains.
As people who support Osman Bey grow..
The battles will increase as well.
Islam will exceed borders.
if Allah permits.
What do you think about..
Many scholars coming to our land, Aktemur Bey?
We will be a free beylik soon.
We will establish a new order.
And this will be realized with scholars.
That is why..
The caravan coming from Konya is important.
We will protect them with our lives for the prosperity.
There is no one going or coming from the horizon.
I hope nothing happened to them.
Kutlu, send troops to Konya road.
-Bey.
-Tell them to look for the caravan.
-As you command, Bey.
Aktemur Bey.
Lord's soldiers are going to Konya.
They heard about the group they will attack them.
Then we should be the one who attacks.
Let's get there quickly now,
-and let's ruin their plan!
-We will!
We will not stop until we kill them!
Come on!
Amen.
My father Ertugrul Ghazi,
he spent his life on horseback
with sword in his hand
trying to settle in a land.
We
settled in this land, thank Allah.
This ground in which you are buried,
is now our country.
And without anyone's help.
With Allah's permission,
we broke all of our ties.
We saw that
the one who stays in the shadow cannot have a shadow.
If we stay under someone else's shadow,
how can we be a shadow for the innocent ones?
We took over your holy cause.
We concluded this cause
which holds responsible not for victory
but for the expedition,
with victory, Thank Allah.
And now, with my children
If Allah permits, we will spread
this banner all over the world.
Until the whole world is conquered
we will keep securing order.
Right, children?
You don't have to worry, Ertugrul Bey.
Don't show mercy to anyone!
Kill them all, don't leave anyone alive!
Destroy them all!
The ones who stop Turks lose their heads.
The one who targets my land loses his life!
Don't you know that?
Allah is the greatest!
Defend the wings!
Do not disperse!
My death will not change the prophecy.
We will take back the lands
which belongs to us.
These lands will belong to Turks until the doomsday.
The light of science
spreads fear to the hearts of the enemy.
Infidels intended to put out the light of science.
You arrived on time, brave men.
-Thank you.
-Thank you Dursun Fakih.
The road that is taken
with science ends up with victory.
The land that is taken
with sword is kept with pen, Dursun Fakih.
We will always be the protectors of science.
Thank you.
Alps.
The foundations of the new orde
r we will establish will be laid in Sogut.
Let's bury our martyrs and get going.
To Sogut, not only with Ulema,
but we will also go back there
with the heads of infidels.
Thank you. Come on.
Do you see, Alaca?
He called us but now he's late and making us wait.
Oh, Osman Bey.
What can he do? His horse is slow.
I was thinking,
why my ears are ringing right, Iltutan?
Why do you think?
Ask this to the ones
who have been waiting for you.
Where have you been?
With my children
we went to my father for the good news.
I was going to take you too
but you were trying to put Halime to sleep,
so I didn't want to bother you.
All right, tell me, Osman Bey.
Since you have made us wait
and called us all the way here,
I hope it is something worthwhile.
Nothing.
I just wanted to race.
It seems you can't get enough of defeat at all.
Look at you. Look at you.
When did we lose?
You have lost now, you'll see.
Wait a second, wait.
But this race
will be different from the other ones.
Why is that?
You'll see it if you win.
You're making me wonder, is that so?
Alaca, do you hear?
He's making us curious.
Let's win and see, girl.
Iltutan, look at me, we have to win.
Do you hear me?
She's curious, if we lose...
Look at me, let's get this done.
Come on.
O Allah.
-Come on now.
-Come on!
You were a young branch of
a glorious plane tree.
Now you are becoming strong enough
for the trunk of that tree.
You know that, right?
Mother, I know.
It is the memento of your late grandfather.
Let a part of him affect you too.
I'll protect it at all costs.
My brave son.
You carry your father's heart
and his mind.
I know you will protect all the mementos at all costs.
Now Osman Bey
is declaring all over the world
that he is an independent Bey.
When the time comes
both this Beylik and its cause
will be yours.
At that moment
it will be time for you to bear fruits
in your branches that are strong.
In the cause of the name of Allah...
...always have mercy and justice...
...in your heart, son.
Your word is an amulet in my heart, mother.
I'll always bear it.
Your mother will always be here.
Don't forget.
Come on alps, come on. Hurry up, please.
Osman Bey is expecting to see everyone in Sogut.
I don't know how can I make it on time.
Come on Ulgen, we're leaving.
Gather the supplies and follow us.
It's almost over Malhun Hatun.
We will load a few more sacks and we'll set out.
Thank you.
Alps, get the horses ready!
Come on, come on.
No, no. It's nowhere to be found!
My Gurbuz is nowhere to be found,
I looked everywhere.
Do you mean the alp one or goat one?
Mother, Cerkutay
gave it to alps,
maybe they're feeding them, it will come back.
That Cerkutay!
If he hurts my child even a bit
you'll see what I'm going to do to him!
Mother, it's just a goat, why would he hurt it?
Oh Cerkutay, don't you know my mother?
-Is it over?
-The car is ready Ulgen Hatun.
We loaded them.
Thank you Yagiz Alp. Mother, come on.
We need to go to Sogut,
we have lots of work to do.
I said Gurbuz but you keep saying Sogut!
Right, alps.
Did you see my child, my Gurbuz, my goat?
Kara Ebe.
Are you looking for the big goat that
was taken to Sogut to be slaughtered?
To be slaughtered?
Cerkutay!
Cerkutay! Cerkutay!
Cerkutay! Cerkutay'
Praise be, praise be!
Parise be, my Bala.
The time is passing
but you still remember, is that so, Osman Bey?
Of course I do.
Do you remember it?
The time will come
our tent will be filled with the voice of our children.
Then the holy state of the Turkish tribes
that come together, will be established.
The reputation of the order of
justice and freedom
will be heard from afar.
With the women raised by Bala Hatun
and with the soldiers of Osman Bey
we will plant our banners all over.
With Allah's permission,
we will see those days my Bala.
I hope so, Osman.
My Bala.
-Osman.
-Come here.
It looks great.
It's so pretty.
It looks well.
You were always with me in my dreams.
You haven't broken our vows since the first day.
You have always supported me with your sisters.
Thank you.
I believe in your dreams j
ust as I believed in you, Osman.
Thankfully all of them
are coming true one by one.
Our dreams are coming true.
See, the past stays right here.
I was Osman and I was with you,
I became Osman Bey and I'm still with you.
But now
it is our time to declare independence.
We will let all the world know
that we are an independent Beylik.
-Is it over now, Osman?
-No.
Can the dreams end at all?
It's just a beginning.
-Come on. Come on my Bala.
-Come on.
Thank you.
Even though the tree branches out
the great joy takes place
in the places that are near the roots, right?
After all, its branches lean towards the trunk.
You're right Malhun Hatun, but
the real matter is that the trunk and
branches are tied to each other so tight.
Root, feeds well. That is why, Esrigun Hatun.
And root is..
Us, these people.
Everyone that supports Osman Bey.
However..
They all know the hardships
Osman Bey endured to come here.
They know that, Osman Bey's road..
Is the Road of Allah.
That is why they fight without asking.
How strange.
I never think of Osman Bey
getting orders from someone else.
It is like being a Bey
was given to him from birth.
Every tree has its time of
being a sapling, Esrigun Hatun.
And Osman Bey..
Fought a lot of hardships to become Bey.
Those hardships are so bad that..
One is even from your own people.
His uncle.
Don't you worry uncle.
There will not be a single traitor in this tribe.
I will kill..
All of them.
Now think about what happened..
To those who tried to trick me.
Those who do not want to
have the same consequences..
Will act accordingly.
Being Bey means..
Getting rid of poisonous vines
so that the tree can grow.
I bear witness that...
....no one deserves
to be worshiped except Allah...
and I bear witness that Muhammad...
is the Messenger of Allah.
Osman Bey got rid of them.
He killed even his uncle..
Who was a traitor of Islam's way.
He took one life from him.
Being Bey means, withstanding this fire.
Osman Bey withstood them all.
Who knows what Osman Bey
went through outside..
Since he lived so much inside.
How did he took Turkmens, Greeks..
And Christian people against him.
No matter the Lord or the Commander..
From now on, Inhisar is..
Kayi's, Turk's property.
It is Islam's property.
Allah is the greatest!
Osman Bey won against them all.
Many conquests he made,
many infidel lands a homeland.
However..
He never lifted a finger among the wronged in them.
Osman Bey followed Sunnah.
Because he ruled..
All the people with mercy.
When our Rasulullah (PBUH)..
Saw a jewish funeral..
Used to stood up out of respect.
He knew that living together..
And seeing each other as a person first.
Osman Bey knew that first as well.
As he listened the problems of
people of the mosque..
He listened the..
People from the church the same.
He came up with solutions.
Does he put laws? Of course.
We all have boundaries.
We invite.
Tell about Islam.
Those who like it come and those who don't..
As long as they show respect to our beliefs..
Can live with us in peace.
There is no forcing in Islam.
We do not torment who does not as well.
We act on what people deserve.
We always have our swords on tormenters necks..
And our hands on the wronged ones.
We always follow the Sunnah of Rasulullah (PBUH).
Those who follow Sunnah..
Even if they go through
many hardships like Osman Bey..
Always stand on the way of Allah.
May Allah always help us follow Sunnah.
-Amin.
We are such lucky people that..
The words of Rasulullah (PBUH)
untie all the knots inside of us.
And not only us..
Also those who do not believe.
That is peace.
May Allah always provides this peace..
To the beylik of Osman Bey.
Amin.
Mother.
Mother, look I made bread for you.
Praise be, my angel daughter.
Let me have a look.
It is so beautiful. Thank you.
Enjoy it.
How do you do all those things?
Both motherhood and martialism.
Your heart must be strong
to be a sister, Esrigun Hatun.
Our aim is to protect our home,
family and homeland.
Parise be.
If we lose our homeland..
...who will call us mother, Esrigun Hatun?
Our power comes from motherhood.
Don't you think about getting married?
No.
-My sword...
-No one is telling you to drop your sword.
But..
...motherhood is in the nature of women.
When we prepare the sherbets,
everything will be ready, Malhun Hatun.
Praise be my Ulgen.
Thank you for your efforts, Sisters.
Thank you Malhun Hatun.
Ulgen.
Where is Dark Midwife?
She is still looking for the goat.
Welcome!
Hatun!
Don't come.
I came.
Don't come. Don't come.
Come.
Ulgen.
Don't come. Don't come.
Why are you coming? Run. Save yourself.
-What happened Hatun?
-Go, save yourself. I'll tell you later.
Did you bring that for me?
Go now! Run! I'll tell you later!
-What happened?
-Just go! I'll tell you!
You damned man! -Mother...
-Mother..
-You blood shedder.
You sinister!
Mother, stop! Ulgerv what is happening?
Come here! How could you hurt my child? -Mother...
-Now I will hurt you!
-Yes, hurt me mother. I got used to it!
Ulgen, what happened?
Tell me first! What happened?!
You killed my Gurbuz!
You have blood on your hands!
My Gurbuz is gone!
My child is gone!
Mother..
Mother, I sent it to the mansion.
I guess they brought it here and sacrificed it.
It's not around.
My Gurbuz is gone!
My child is gone!
-Mother don't..
-My child is gone!
I'm all done!
I am done! What am I going to do?
Kill me now!
My heart is in flames!
Mother..
Mother, don't... Don't upset yourself, please...
Look, I will find a better Gurbuz for you,
I will find a bigger, a greater one.
Are you making fun of me?
Do you see, Ulgen?
Mother... Mother..
So that I lost my child..
...then...
...you also don't have my daughter! Come!
Mother, I won't give her to you!
-No!
There is now blood between us.
I won't give you my daughter!
You killed my child!
Towba towba! Mother, you talk like you
lost your mind. What child are you talking about?
Ulgen walk!
Mother... Don't be crazy.
What do you want from Cerkutay?
Mother, we couldn't see each other since I came here.
Give my daughter to me!
I won't give my daughter to you!
Dark Midwife.
I caught the little boy.
My dear... My child is here.
My Gurbuz.
My child..
Did you come?
Your son-in-law was almost going to kill him*
My golden haired boy...
Gurbuz..
Do not mess with me from now on,
otherwise you'll lose your place.
Come on, Osman Bey is waiting.
Thank you.
Live long, thank you, thank you.
Brokers are announcing all over.
Everyone will know.
The one whose heart is burning with
the fire of holy war is now independent.
Osman Bey, son of Ertugrul Ghazi,
establish his Beylik.
He has become a sovereign Bey
who does not pay taxes to anyone.
A khutbah has been delivered
in the name of Osman Bey,
and became an independent Bey.
It has no ties with anyone.
Osman Bey has officially established his Beylik.
He has become a sovereign Bey
who does not pay taxes to anyone.
Allah tells the truth.
We opened
many councils
in the name of Allah Who held us responsible for
the expedition, not for the victory.
And now that expedition
concluded with victory.
It is our duty to be grateful.
In the name of Allah.
O' servants of Allah.
The path is clear for those who want it.
The evidents are in sight for those who listen.
Death
has eradicated many more before you.
It has taken those
who are more powerful than you
to the graveyard.
By their death
their comfort and joy ended.
The fact that
we're here and happy today
is the result of us obeying Allah
Who is the One and Absolute,
and
of us following his Prophet's sunna.
Thus we have been granted the secret that
this is a blessing from your Rabb.
O' my Allah,
bestow this upon us
for the sake of your Beloved One.
Oh my Creator.
let Osman Ghazi Han's Sultanate
be blessed.
Amen.
-Amen.
Read Al-Fatiha Surah.
Make way!
Osman Bey!
Osman, the Ghazi of Ghazis
delivered the khutbah,
Osman, the protector of the innocent ones
destroyed the cruel ones.
Osman hit the infidel on their chests!
It is time to be an independent Bey!
He punished the cruel
for the sake of martyrs!
He turned the tribe into a city
and formed his council out of nothing!
Bey Osman, it is time to be a Han!
It is time to be an independent Bey!
From our homelands
we rode all the way to these lands.
We fought.
We defeated many of them.
We lost against many of them.
Our purpose was to turn these lands
into our country.
And we
took these lands, Thank Allah.
Thank Allah.
-Thank Allah.
From now on, we will not stop.
If we stop,
then we will only deteriorate.
We will keep conquering new lands.
We will walk.
We will take a step, so we can be
a homeland to the poor.
From now on..
...nothing will be like before.
My Bey.
We hit the Lord and the army of Byzantium.
But... Valens is still alive.
He can be alive.
We hit the army.
We made Byzantium lose its power.
They cannot come and attack us now.
But..
...if they try attacking us...
...then they will face the most talented
warriors in our castles.
Tell me.
Why did we take those castles?
To spread justice.
Then... now.
...we will give those places to people
whose fairness we trust.
Vural Alp.
Come.
Boran.
My Bey.
From now on..
..Kopruhisar is your property.
Rule it with justice.
The order is given by my Bey,
and the duty will be fulfilled, my Bey.
Thank you.
Konur.
Koyunhisar...
...is now your property.
Rule with mercy.
Your entrustment is my entrustment, my Bey.
Thank you.
Cerkutay...
My Bey.
I told you that I would give you a house.
So...
..Itburnu..
...is now your property.
Rule with merit.
It is your entrustment, my Bey.
Thank you.
Beys.
Come.
Gorkluce...
...bring it.
From now on..
...we will unite under one flahg.
My Bey...
There is no Cavundur's Bayindir now.
There is Kayi's Bayindir.
Thank you.
My Bey.
Now we will fight under one flag.
Thank you.
- Thank you my Bey.
- Live long.
Here.
- Thank you my bey.
- Thank you, thank you.
Thank you, live long.
Beys.
And Alps.
Are gathered under one banner.
Those who are in east..
And those who are in west will know that..
Those who live in these lands are free.
And we take our freedom..
From our Beylik.
If something happens..
To someone in these lands..
They will know that..
Osman Bey will surely get revenge.
Those whose courage comes from Islam..
Make your heart calm and your arm strong.
I vow that..
We will not stop..
Before having our rule in the world
and the world is our land.
Allah is the greatest!
Thank you, thank you,
live long.
I am grateful.
Let us..
Sit at the tables.
Let us sit.
Boran.
Bey.
Play the kopuz.
So that..
May the whole world hear the voice of Turks.
As my Bey commands.
Let's go. In the name of Allah,
the most merciful, the most compassionate.
This state's Governor is Osman Bey Ghazi...
Everyone around the world will know who he is.
Thanks to the state that
was given to Osman by Allah..
The world will find peace again.
Thanks to the state that
was given to Osman by Allah..
The world will find peace again.
The spark that fell into the heart of Osman..
Will remain in the hearts of others for centuries.
Thanks to the state that
was given to Osman by Allah..
The world will find peace again.
Thanks to the state that
was given to Osman by Allah..
The world will find peace again.
Allah's decision will let..
His state's borders expand.
Thanks to the state that was given to Osman by Allah..
The world will find peace again.
This state's hands will reach the poor like silk..
And it will punch the cruel with its strong fists.
Thanks to the state that was given to Osman by Allah..
The world will find peace again.
Hey praise be!
Visit our website for more: turkision.com
See you next season!